剧情回顾
Previously on Lost
你偷了我的肾...
You stole my kidney...
你需要一个父亲  我需要一个肾
You needed a father,and I needed a kidney.
忘了这些吧
Get over it.
我知道你是被领养的
I know you were raised in Foster Care.
我知道你在来这岛上的4年前
I know you spent the four years
都是坐轮椅的
prior to your arrival on this island in a wheelchair,
我还知道你是怎么坐上轮椅的
And I know how you ended up in it.
如果我告诉你在这座岛上有...
What if I told you that somewhere on this island,
一个巨大的盒子
there's a very large box,
不管你怎么想象 那里面到底是什么
and whatever you imagined,whatever you wanted to be in it,
当你打开时 那东西就在你眼前
When you opened that box,there it would be?
我说那盒子里最好
I'd say I hope that box is big enough
是你的新潜艇
to imagine yourself up new submarine.
John你真的说到做到了
Well, John, you've really gone and done it now.
你不会又要
You're not
和我说你那个神奇的盒子了?
about the magic box Agc Bo are you?
不  John我要给你看那里面到底是什么
No, John. I'm gonna show you what came out of it.
爸爸?
Dad?
省点力气吧
Save your breath.
没人会听见的
Nobody's gonna hear you.
8天之前
8 days ago
爸爸?
Dad?
这是怎么回事?
What is this?
你说呢? 你把他带来的
You tell me.You brought him here.
怎么会是我?
I didn't bring him here.
小心点John 别靠近他
I'd be careful about getting too close to him,John.
你们在哪找到他的? 为什么把他带到这里来?
Well, where did you find him? Why did you bring him here?
我已经说过了 我们没有...
I've already said...  We didn't--
你想让我问他吗?
You want me to ask him how he got here?
随便你
Be my guest.
Tom!
我已经警告过你了 John
I warned you, John.
你不明白吗 John?
Don't you know, John?
你不明白我们在哪里吗?
Don't you know where we are?
他是什么意思?
What did he mean?
恐怕我们没时间...
I'm afraid we don't have time
来讨论这件事了 John
To deal with that right now,John.
我们所有人一早就要离开
We're leaving first thing in the morning,all of us.
去哪儿?
Where are you going?
去个新地方
We're going to a new place.
严格的说 是个很老的地方
Well,an old place,actually.
想和我们一起去吗?
Would you like to come with us?
好啊
Yes.
很好
Good.
Kate被我们关在 前面的一个屋子里
We're holding Kate a few buildings over from here.
也许你可以和她告个别
Maybe you'd like to say good-bye.
你去哪?
Hey, where you going?
我在自己的帐篷里才睡的着
I can't sleep if I'm not in my own tent.
那我们去你那边
Fine.Let's go to your tent.
我不是针对你  但...
It's nothing personal. It's...
老习惯了
Old habits, you know?
好吧  你快走吧
Fine. Scram.
要我陪你回家吗?
You want me to walk you home?
我想我自己能行
It's five tents.I think I'll make it.
你肯定吗?反正我要上个厕所
Are you sure? I gotta pee anyway.
真浪漫
That is so romantic.
你们在干什么?
What the hell y'all doin'?
你又在干什么?
What the hell you doing?
去解个手
Going to take a leak.
我们也是啊
Yeah, well, so are we.
那没问题
Well, all righty then.
你好 James
Hello, James.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：   许愿  后期：梁良 双语字幕：七色九天
你拉链没拉好
You wanna zip your pants up?
你在这里做什么?
What the hell are you doing here?
我是来找你的
Looking for you, actually.
好啊  泰山 你把能让我们...
Okay, Tarzan.So now
离开这座岛的...
that you're back From your "Blow Up
潜艇给炸飞了
Everything That could get us F The Island" Tour,
你来告诉我 你什么时候
How 'bout you tell me why
投靠他们了?
you joined up With the damn enemy?
我没有加入他们 我打入他们的内部
I Didn't join 'em.I infiltrated 'em.
-你在做卧底?    -没错
-You're undercover with the others.  -That's right.
给我一个相信你的理由
No how 'bout you give me one reason to believe that?
我钻进了Ben的帐篷 绑架了他
I snuck into Ben's tent and kidnapped him.
我把他拽进了丛林
I tiedim up, dragged him off into the jungle.
你大老远的回来告诉我是因为...
And you came all the way back here to tell me this because...
因为他折磨了你...
Because this is the same man who tortured you,
打了你  侮辱了你...
Beat you, humiliated You...
我要你杀了他
And I want you to kill him.
你想让他死 就自己下手吧
You want him dead,you kill him.
-我不是杀人犯   -我也不是
-I'm not a murderer.  -Neither am I.
除了你在悉尼杀的那个人
Except for the man you killed in Sydney.
他们有我们的资料James
They got files on us, James...
所有人的
All of us.
那他们都错了
Yeah, well,their files got their facts wrong.
看来我不该来找你
Then I made a mistake coming to you.
别告诉其他人我来过
Please don't tell anyone that I was here.
停下!
Hey, stop!
你给我停下!
I said stop!
该死的  等等!
Damn it! Wait up!
3天之前
这样应该能行
There. That ought to do it.
谢谢
Thanks.
我自己做的话要好几个小时
That would've taken me hours to do myself.
很高兴我能帮上忙
Glad I could help.
别介意他们
Don't mind them.
你来他们都很兴奋
They're all just excited you're here.
兴奋?
Excited?
我们一直在等待你
We've been waiting for you.
John 你有空吗?
John, you got a minute?
当然
Yeah.
Ben找你过去
Ben's asking for you.
好吧
Okay.
Ben 这是星期6早晨6点
Ben, it's 6:00 a.m. on saturday morning.
Kwon怀孕了 胎儿很健康
Kwon is pregnant.The fetus is healthy
她在这里受孕
and was conceived on island with her husband.
他丈夫之前不能生育...
He was sterile when they got here.
John 谢谢你能来
Hello, John. Thanks for coming.
那是什么?
What's that?
Juliet正在你原来的营地搜集情报
Juliet is gathering information for us at your former camp.
如果那里有谁怀孕的话...
She's determing if any of the women are pregnant.
我们就过去...
Then we're gonna go in and...
劫持他们
take them.
劫持他们?
Take them?
我们干这个已经不是第一次了John
This is not the first time we've done this.
相信我 我们不会伤害任何人的
Trust me, no one will get hurt.
能把那个递给我吗?
Could you pass me that, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我要对你表示感激 John
I believe I have you to thank for this, John.
一周前我的脚趾还动不了...
A week ago, I couldn't move my toes...
而当你一出现
But the minute you showed up,
我就有酸痛的感觉
I started to feel pins and needles.
而这只是开始 John
And this is only the beginning, John.
我等不及要让你瞧瞧 这座岛到底能做什么
I can't wait to show you what this island can do,
但不幸的是
but unfortunately,
你还没有准备好 John
you're not ready, John.
不  我准备好了
No, I'm ready.
不  John你没有
No, John, you're not.
你还是那个瘫痪的人
You're still crippled by the memories of the man you used to be before you came to this island,
这样你永远得不到解脱
and you'll never be free
直到你解脱你父亲 给你带来的痛苦
until you release the hold that your father has over you.
你为什么要把他带到这里来?
Why do you think you brought him here?
那个神奇的盒子
The magic box.
好了 Ben 为什么你不...
Okay, Ben, how about you show me...
"神奇的盒子"只是一个暗喻 John
"Magic box" is a metaphor, John.
我不能让你看 直到你...
I can't show you anythinguntil you can show me
愿意成为我们的人
that you're ready and willing to be one of us.
当人们加入我们的时候
When people join us here on this island,
他们需要作出某种姿态
they need to make a gesture
他们的愿望 他们的承诺
of free will, of commitment.
那就是为什么 你要杀了你的父亲
That's why you're gonna have to kill your father.
你们什么时候回来的?
When did you get back?
昨晚吧
Last night.
...今天一早
Well, early this morning.
野营咯?
So... camping, huh?
你们在那里干什么?
What were you guys doing out there?
我们想去探险
We...figured we'd explore a bit,
看看那边的海滩有什么
you know,see what was further down the beach.
培养培养友情
Male bonding.
下次你们去的时候 算我一个
Well, next time you go out, sign me up.
下一次  当然
Yeah, next time. Sure.
谢谢 Jin
Thanks, Jin.
我们必须告诉Jack
We have to tell Jack.
是啊  也能让他看看她的伤势
Yeah, I mean,shouldn't he check out her wound?
你能保证我们能相信Jack吗?
Can you give me your word that Jack can be trusted?
他和他们在一起已经10多天了
That he spent ten days with those people
难道什么也没发生吗?
and that nothing happened to him?
-还有那个整天和他粘在一起的女人...   -Juliet
And that woman he's spending all his time with... -Juliet.
Juliet  2周之前她还把你们的朋友关在笼子里
Aye. Juliet. Two weeks ago,she had your friends in cages.
Naomi...
你听见她说的话了
Well, you heard everything that she said.
如果我们能保证她的安全
If we keep her safe,
她就可以帮我们离开这里
she's our way off this island.
这样的话 你相信Jack
So given that,do you trust Jack,
还是不相信?
or don't you?
好啊
Right.
我们要找一个信得过的人
So we better bring in someone we can trust.
你该穿双鞋子
You should've put some shoes on.
你认为呢?
You think?
那里面还有什么?
So what else is in it?
什么里面?
In what?
我的资料
The file they got on me.
也不多
Not much.
你父母在你很小的时候就过世了
That your parents died when you were very young.
但不知道为什么
But it doesn't say why
你父亲杀了你母亲...
your father...shot your mother...
然后又杀了自己
or why he turned the gun on himself.
对你来说一定很痛苦
That must've been hard for you.
还有呢?
What else?
高中的记录...
High school transcripts...
犯罪记录...
criminal record...
那些你因为骗人而被捕的记录
all the con jobs you were arrested for.
这就是你为什么要用假名字了
I guess that's why you use an alias, huh?
为什么起Sawyer这个名字呢?
Why did you choose the name Sawyer?
你以为我很傻吗?
How stupid do you think I am?
我已经被Ben骗过一次了
I already been conned by Ben once.
也许你听说过那只作过记号的小兔子
Maybe you heard about it...bunny with a number painted on it?
你以为我会跟你走进丛林?
You think I'm just gonna follow you through the jungle?
James求你了 你必须得相信我
Please, you have to...You have to trust me.
你要把我带去哪里? 跟我说实话!
Where are you taking me? Tell me the truth!
-你要我干什么?  -我已经和你说过了...
-What do you want from me?   -I'm bringing you there to do exactly what I said...
-让你杀了Ben   -为什么找我?
-To kill Ben.  -Why did you come back to get me?
-我没有选择  -为什么是我?你干嘛不下手?!
-I had to.   -Why me?! Why won't you do it yourself?
-James求你了...   -别叫我James!
-James, please... -Don't call me James!
为什么你自己不下手?
Why won't you do it yourself?
因为我不能!我做不了!
Because I can't! I can't!I can't do it!
所以我就回来找你
That's why I came back for you.
起来
Get up.
我会跟你去你抓他的地方
I'll go to wherever you got him,
但我们要把他带回我们的营地
but then we're bringing him back to our camp.
我不会杀任何人的 你知道吗?
I ain't killing nobody.You understand me?
是啊  我了解...
Yeah. I understand...
但你会改变主意的
But you'll change your mind
当你听到他所说的话
When you hear what he has to say,
你会改变主意的
you'll change your mind.
伙计
Hey, dude.
Hello,Hurley
你能保密吗?
Can you keep a secret?
你们已经和她谈过了?
You've already spoken to her?
但你最好自己听一下
Yeah, but you're gonna want to hear it for yourself.
你们还没有告诉Jack?
And you haven't told Jack?
是的
No.
很好
Good.
我叫Sayid Jarrah
My name's Sayid Jarrah.
我知道你的直升机坠毁在这座岛上了
I understand your helicopter crashed onto the island.
严格来说 是坠毁在海里了
Actually, it crashed in the water.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
Naomi  Naomi Dorrti
Naomi你是从哪里来的?
Naomi, from where exactly did you take off?
一艘船 一艘货船
A ship... freighter...
大约80海里朝西
About 80 nautical miles west of here.
我是一个搜寻小队的成员
I'm part of a search and recovery team.
你告诉我朋友815航班的残骸已经被找到了?
You told my friends the wreckage of flight 815 was discovered.
你的意思是部分残骸?
Did you mean the partial wreckage?
他们在巴里岛找到了整架飞机
No. They found the entire plane off the coast of Bali,
在4英里下的海沟里
in an ocean trench 4 miles deep.
他们派机器潜艇下去探测
They sent down cameras in these little robots
来观测残骸
to survey the wreck.
他们发现了所有尸体
The bodies were all there.
很明显我们还没死
Well, obviously we're not dead.
是啊
Obviously.
你不是来找我们的
So if you weren't looking for us,
那你是来找谁的?
then who were you looking for?
他
Him.
Desmond?
我们的公司受雇于一个叫Penelope Wiemore的女人
My company was hired by a woman named Penelope Widmore.
我不知道为什么 我从没见过她
I don't know why. I never met her.
她给了我们这个坐标
She gave us a set of coordinates.
我们就朝着这个
We've been conducting
GPS差异标进行搜索
a differential G.P.S. grid search ever since.
你知道这座岛?
You knew about the island?
岛? 这个坐标...
Island? We were given coordinates
在大洋的中间
in the middle of the bloody ocean.
我们以为收到了错位的指令
We thought it was a fool's errand...
直到3天前
till three days ago.
当我准备飞回那艘船时 突然间...
I was flying back for the ship,when all of a sudden
云开雾散 我看见了陆地
the clouds cleared, and I saw land.
仪表开始打转
The instruments started spinning.
我意识到飞机在下落
I realized I was going down,
所以我弃机跳伞了
so I grabbed my chute, and I bailed.
你看见她的直升机了吗?
Did you actually see her helicopter?
没有
No.
你认为我在撒谎吗  老兄?
You think I'm lying, mate?
我想你没有办法
I take it you have no means whatsoever
和你们的货船联系吧?
of communicating with that freighter of yours?
你叫什么名字? Sayid?
What was your name? Sayid?
没错
Yes.
不要忘了我救了你Sayid
Remind me not to rescue you, Sayid.
你说我听了Ben说的话
So Ben...You said I'd kill him
就会杀了他咯?
when I heard what he's got to say.
-是啊     -你不给我点建议吗?
-that's right.  -Well, you wanna give me a heads-up?
这由不得我来说
It's not really my place to tell you.
你在资料上读到的...
Look, what you read in that file...
悉尼的那个人
about the guy in Sydney...
我弄错人了
I thought he was someone else.
我犯了个错误 我想杀的不是他
I made a mistake.I didn't mean to kill him.
那你想杀的是谁?
Well, who'd you mean to kill?
我们快到了吗?
Are we almost there?
快了
Almost.
3天之前
快起来John
Wake up, John.
是时候了
It's time.
我知道这不容易 但越快越好
I know it won't be easy,but the quicker the better.
你开玩笑吧?
You're kidding me, right?
你想要他杀了我?
You expect him to kill me?
John?
你现在犹豫是因为...
The hesitation that you're feeling
你认为他偷走你的肾
is just the part of you
是理所当然的
that still feels like he has a perfectly good explanation for stealing your kidney,
然后把你从8层楼摔下去
throwing you out of an 8-story window.
你不想解脱吗?
Don't you wanna be free from him?
他犹豫是因为他懦弱...
The hesitation he's feeling is because he is a spineless...
闭嘴!
Shut up!
-我需要想想       -别想了 John
-I gotta think... -Don't think, John.
你在浪费时间  大眼男
You're wasting your time, bug-eye.
我和他经历了这些
Me and him have been through all this.
-他要的只有他老爸...   -闭嘴  我让你闭嘴!
-All he wants is his daddy... -Shut up! I said shut up!
你还没想明白吗?
You really haven't figured it out yet,have you?
结束这一切吧John
Let go of him, John.
你为什么要这样对我?
Why are you doing this to me?
这么做是为了你自己 只要他还在喘息
You're doing this to yourself.As long as he's still breathing,
你就还是那个可怜悲哀的人
you'll still be that same sad, pathetic little man
还被旅行社赶走
that was kicked off his walkabout tour
因为你不能走路
because you couldn't walk.
这周我一直在这里John
I'll be here the rest of the week, John,
如果你改变了主意...
if you change your mind...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
他不是我们想的那个人
He's not who we thought he was.
狗娘养的...
Son of a...
这可是个好地方啊 Locke
Nice place you got here, Locke.
Ben就在里面
Ben's inside in the brig.
你准备好了?
You ready?
是的  准备好了
Yeah, I'm ready.
你的朋友?
Friends of yours?
这是一艘19世纪中叶的奴隶船
It's an old slaving ship,mid nineteenth century,
我猜他们...
My guess is they...
把这些奴隶抓来
captured the slaves and brought them here
到这座岛上来开矿
to try and mine the island.
这箱子里是什么?
What's in the boxes?
都是炸药
That'd be dynamite.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
你真的抓住那个杂种了?
You really kidnapped the little bastard.
我们不能杀了他 Locke
We ain't killin' him, Locke.
随你怎么说 James
Whatever you say, James.
瞧瞧啊
Well, well, well.
你干什么?!
What are you doing?!
快开门啊!
Open the damn door!
闭嘴!
Shut up!
开门啊!
Open up!
我让你闭嘴!
I said shut up!
你是谁?
Who the hell are you?
-这就像个无线电?     -没错!
-It's like a radio?  -It's like a radio, yes,
但我还没见过这么尖端的设备
but I've never seen equipment this sophisticated.
-但你能修好它的是吗? -希望如此
-But you can still make it work, right?  -I hope so.
那其他部分呢?
And what about the other part?
他们找到了飞机 我们全死了?
The part about they found the plane and we're all dead?
先别管那个
One thing at a time.
这不是个单向音频频道
There's not a single audible channel.
无论是什么在干扰
Whatever that interference is,
都在阻止我们发信号出去
it's blocking our ability to send our own transmission.
如果...
If we...
那是什么?  无线电吗?
What's that? Is that a radio?
你们在哪找到的?
Where'd you get it?
在行李里
Uh, the luggage.
什么  你们在行李里找到了个无线电?
What, you just found a radio in the luggage?
Kate如果我说出来 你要保密
Kate, if I explain,I want you to keep this very quiet.
保什么密?
Keep what very quiet?
Locke!快打开那该死的门!
Locke! Open the damn door!
快开门  我能听见你 你个死秃顶!
Open it up! I can hear you,you bald bastard!
Rousseau?
Locke
什么风把你吹到"黑岩"来了?
What brings you to "The Black Rock"?
炸药  你呢?
Dynamite. And you?
快开门!
Open this door!
开门啊!
Open up!
箱子就在那边
Crates are right over there.
快开门啊!
Open this damn door!
小心点  炸药很不稳定
Be careful. It's unstable.
Locke! Locke!
两天之前
很美不是吗?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
无论你在这岛上多久
No matter how much time you spend on the island,
你永远也不会厌倦这种景致的
you just never get tired of this view.
我们还没有自我介绍过
We haven't been formally introduced.
我叫Richard
I'm Richard.
你介意我坐下吗?
You mind if I join you?
当然不
Oh, sure.
他想要你难堪
He wanted to embarrass you.
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
Ben知道你不会杀了自己的亲生父亲
Ben knew you weren't gonna kill your own father.
他让整个营地的人都来看
He put you in front of everyone in our camp
就是为了看你失败
just so they could all watch you fail.
为什么?
Why?
大家都在说
'cause when word got back here
一个脊柱瘫痪的人
that there was a man with a broken spine on the plane
突然又能走路了...
who could suddenly walk again, well...
人们开始很兴奋
People here began to get very excited,
因为这...
because that...
只会发生在...
That could only happen to someone
一个特别特殊的人身上
who was extremely special.
Ben不愿大家这么认为 John
Now Ben doesn't want anyone to think you're special,John.
你为什么要告诉我这些?
And why are you telling me this?
Ben在浪费我们的时间
Ben has been wasting our time
一直在钻研怀孕这件事
with novelties like fertility problems.
我们需要有人提醒我们
We're looking for someone to remind us
我们在这里是为了一个更重要的原因
that we're here for more important reasons.
你要我干什么?
What do you want from me?
我需要你找到自己的目的
I want for you to find your purpose,
然后去实施它
and to do that,
你父亲就是牺牲品 John
your father has to go, John,
你如果下不了手的话...
and since you're not going to do it...
我建议你找另一个人
I'm gonna suggest someone else.
Sawyer?
Sawyer怎么会杀了我父亲? 他甚至都不认识他
Why would Sawyer kill my father?He doesn't even know him.
读下去
Keep reading.
打开着该死的门!
Open this damn door!
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
我用枪指着你 John
I'm pointin' my gun at you, John-boy.
你只有3秒钟来打开这扇门
You got three seconds to open this door!
你不会射任何人的James
You're not gonna shoot anyone, James.
1...
One...
2!
two!
如果那枪里有子弹的话
If there were any bullets in that gun,
干嘛还要用我的刀 架着我的喉咙呢?
why would you hold a knife to my throat?
狗娘养的东西!
Son of a bitch!
看来我没白养这个蠢蛋
Guess I didn't raise no dummies.
-你在说什么?  -意思是那个"死秃顶"
-What the hell's that mean? -It means that "bald-headed bastard"
门外的就是我的儿子
outside the door is my son.
再说一遍
Come again?
我的儿子 我是他的父亲
My son. As in I'm his father.
你懂英语吧?
You do speak English?
你是...
You're...
你是怎么来到这座岛的?
How did you get here... to the island?
岛?
Island?
好吧
Okay.
我沿着I-10公路经过Tallahassee 突然砰的一声...
I'm driving down I-10 through Tallahassee, when bam...
有人出现在了我的后座
Somebody slams into the back of my car.
我以每小时70公里的速度撞了车
I go right into the divider at 70 miles an hour.
我知道的下一件事是...
The next thing I know,
护理人员在给我包扎
the paramedics are strapping me to a gurney,
在救护车里给我注射
stuffing me in the back of an ambulance,
有一个人还朝我微笑
and one of them actually smiles at me as he pops the I.V. In my arm,
然后...什么都没有了
and then... nothing.
一片漆黑
Just black.
我在一个漆黑的房间里醒来
And the next thing I know,I wake up in a dark room
浑身被绑着  嘴里也塞了东西 当门打开
tied up, gag in my mouth,and when the door opens,
我看到了那个被我扔出窗户的人
I'm looking up at the same man I threw out a window...
John Locke
我的死儿子
my dead son.
他"死"了是因为你把他扔出了窗户?
And he's dead 'cause you threw him out a window?
他幸存了下来 只是残废了
No, he survived that,but it paralyzed him,
永久性的
permanently.
他的死是因为他所乘坐的飞机
He's dead because the plane he was flying on
坠毁在了太平洋
crashed in the Pacific.
给你一个坏消息
Well, I got bad news for you, pops,
我和你儿子在同一架飞机上
'cause I was on that plane with your son,
而且他根本没有残废
and he sure as hell wasn't crippled.
我们没有坠毁在太平洋
And we didn't crash in the pacific.
-我们坠毁在这座岛上    -你肯定这是一座岛吗?
-We crashed here on this island.   -You sure it's an island?
那还能是什么?
Well, what else is it?
这里比天堂可怕多了
Little hot for heaven, isn't it?
好吧  我们死了
Oh, okay, so we're dead.
他们在海底找到了你们的飞机
They found your plane on the bottom of the ocean.
1分钟前我还在车里  1分钟后
One minute I'm in a car wreck,and the next minute
我就来到了丛林当中的海盗船里?
I'm in a pirate ship in the middle of the jungle?
如果这里不是地狱  朋友...
If ts isn't hell, friend...
那我们还会在什么地方?
Then where are we?
你为什么要把Locke扔出窗户?
Why did you throw Locke out a window?
他成了个讨厌的人
He was becoming a nuisance.
我骗了他一个肾
I conned him into giving me one of his kidneys.
他就一直念念不忘
He never got over it.
骗?
Conned?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
骗
Conned.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
-什么?  -你的名字?
-Hmm?   -Your name?
一个骗子的名字有很多
A con man goes by many names, friend.
我用过Alan Seward  Anthony Cooper  Ted MacLaren
I've been Alan Seward,Anthony Cooper,Ten McLaren,
Tom Sawyer Louis Jackson Paul...
Tom Sawyer?
我当时很年轻"HUCK FINN"又很流行...(一部动画片)
I was young, and "Huck Finn" was taken...
而且女士们都很喜欢
And the ladies loved that one.
让我更有魅力
Made me charming.
这样?
Well, how about that?
什么这样?
How about what?
Sawyer也是我的名字
Sawyer's my name, too.
Ben发生什么事了?
Ben, what's going on?
-我们要走了     -走?去哪里?
-We're moving.  -Moving? Where are we going?
我们哪里都不去John
We are not going anywhere,John.
你要留在这里
You are going to stay behind.
还有他也是
You both are going to stay behind.
什么?你们不带走他?
What? You're not taking him?
他是你留下的麻烦John 我们是不会帮你处理的
He's your mess, John. Why would we clean him up?
Ben如果你想要让我难堪...
Ben, if you're trying to put me in my place, or embarrass me...
你怎么会有这么荒唐的想法的?
Where would you get a ridiculous idea like that?
你不能离开我
Well, you can't leave me.
经过了这一切 你不能...
After everything, you can't just...
别告诉我我不能做什么 John
Don't tell me what I can't do, John.
但我认为我很特别
But I thought I was... special.
每个人都会犯错误
Well, everyone makes mistakes.
我们现在就走
We're leaving now.
我们会留下踪迹 让你能跟上来  还有John...
We'll leave a trail...one you can track. And,John,
除非你背着你父亲的尸体回来
unless you're carrying your father's body on your back,
否则不要来打扰我们
don't bother.
你又怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
你有没有去过Alabama的Jasper?
You ever been to Jasper, Alabama?
干嘛?
Why?
你到底有没有去过?
Have you, or haven't you?
我去过Jasper
Yeah, I've been to Jasper.
别告诉我我是你爸
Don't tell me I'm your daddy.
不
No.
你杀了我的爸爸
You killed my daddy.
读一遍
Read it.
"亲爱的Sawyer先生..."
"Dear Mr. Sawyer... "
-这是什么?      -读就是了
-What is this?  -Just read it.
"你不知道我是谁
"You don't know who I am,
但我知道你是谁
but I know who you are,
我也知道你做了什么
and I know what you done.
你和我妈妈上了床
You had sex with my mother
然后你偷走了我爸爸的钱
and then you stole my dad's money all away,
所以他很生气  开枪杀了自己的妻子..."
so he got angry,and he killed my mother... "
"然后又开枪自杀..."
"and then he killed himself... "
全是废话...
bla bla bla
那又怎么样?
So what?
这是你吗? 是你写的这封信?
Is this supposed to be you? You wrote this letter?
等一下
Hey, wait a second.
你用我的名字
Did you take my name
是因为你想报仇吗?
because you were on some kind of revenge kick?
继续读下去
Keep reading.
冷静  冷静
Easy, easy.
还没弄清楚呢
Don't get all worked up.
我骗过很多人...
Look, I ran that con two dozen times.
如果你母亲是...
If your mother was one of the...
Mary
Mary.
她叫Mary
Her name was Mary.
Alabama  Jasper的Mary
Mary from Jasper, Alabama.
我记得她
Yeah, I remember her.
是她求我拿走$38,000的
She practically begged me to take her $38,000
来挽救你母亲可悲的一生
and to rescue her from her sorry little life.
把信读完
You finish the letter.
我只拿走了钱
Look, I only took her money.
你父亲的反应过度又不是我的错
It ain't my fault your dad overreacted.
如果他是自杀的话...
If he pulled the old murder-suicide,
那我敢肯定他就在这里
then I'm sure he's down here somewhere.
-也许你能顺便把信捎给他    -读完它!
-Maybe you could take this up with him.  -Finish it!
好吧
Okay.
你想下地狱吗?
You wanna go to hell?
你想下地狱吗?!
You wanna go to hell?!
谢谢
Thank you.
想念芝士汉堡了吧?
You missing those cheeseburgers yet?
每分每秒都在想念
Only every second.
我要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
行
Okay.
-只和你一个人谈   -没问题
-In private.   -No problem.
你想和我说的 你也能告诉她
Anything you wanna say to me,you can say in front of her.
这个不行
Not this.
-没关系的     -不不  你呆着
-It's okay.   -No, no. You can stay.
你知道吗?  你应该留下
Yeah, you know what? You should stay.
考虑到她就是
Seems only fair, considering that she's the reason
我们为什么不告诉你
no one wants to tell you that there's a woman
-Hurley帐篷里有个昨天跳伞来到这座岛上的女人的原因    -什么?
-in Hurley's tent who parachuted onto the island yesterday.   -What?
一个女人  在飞机坠毁前跳了下来
A woman.She jumped from her chopper before it crashed.
她说她起飞的那艘船
She says that the boat that she took off from
离海岸80英里  如果她能有办法
is about 80 miles off the coast and that if she can find a way
-和那里联系  我们就得救了  -为什么没有人和我说过?
-to contact it,we'll all be rescued!  -Why didn't anyone tell me this?
我已经和你说了 他们不信任你
I already told you... because they don't trust you.
怎么做?
How?
什么怎么做?
How what?
她怎么才能联系她的船?
How is she supposed to contact her boat?
你没听到吗?
Did you hear what I just said?
-Hurley  Chaile  Sayid你的朋友都害怕...  -Kate告诉我
-Hurley, Charlie, Sayid, your friends,are afraid to...  -Kate. How?
她有个无线电
She had a phone-radio thing.
Sayid在试着修理它
Sayid's trying to get it to work.
我们应该告诉她
We should tell her.
-不   -告诉我什么?
-No.  -Tell me what?
-我们应该告诉她       -还不是时候
-We should tell her.  -Not yet.
你可以回去了
You can go back now.
你为什么要这样做?
Why did you do this?
他毁了我的生活
He ruined my life,
也毁了你的
and he ruined yours.
他罪有应得
And he had it coming.
Juliet是个内奸
Juliet is a mole.
-什么?   -她在为Ben做事
-What?   -She's working for Ben.
来找出我们这里谁怀孕了
He sent her back to find out which of our women were pregnant.
3天内他们会来海滩
Three days from now,there's gonna be a raid on the beach,
他们会把他们带走
and they're gonna take them.
他们说不想伤害任何人
They say they don't want anyone to get hurt.
你为什么要告诉我?
Well, why are you telling me?
-让你去警告营地里的人       -你自己去
-So you can warn the camp.  -You warn the camp.
我不打算回我们的营地
I'm not going back.
你还是去做卧底?
You're going back undercover?
我不是卧底 James
No, I was never undercover,James.
现在我走自己的路
I'm on my own journey now.
如果我说Juliet是内鬼 他们也不会相信我的
Even if Juliet is a mole,they ain't gonna believe me.
她第一次出现时 我也是这么说的
I been saying that since she showed up.
现在他们会相信你了
They'll believe you now.
那是真的吗?
Is it true?
什么?
Is What True?
他把你扔出窗户...
That he threw you out a window...
让你残废了?
That you were a cripple?
不在是了
Not anymore.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■